please get close to him
find means
of talking to him
raise these matters
with him
help him be able to observe
Salah
at its time
for example most times most
of us
by the time of Maghrib and
Isha
we are at home
from work
in fact from the time of Fajr
if you are not living in
Lagos
you might not have left for
your
office
I understand that those of
our
brothers in Lagos
some of them even before Fajr
they have left their home to
be
able
to arrive at work
to time
but those outside Lagos it is
possible
for you and many others too
in Lagos
you will be at home for
Salatul
Fajr
for Salatul Maghrib
and Salatul Isha
one way to help your daddy
please be at home
go for those Salat
with him
be at home
go for Salatul Fajr with him
daddy let us go for
Salatul Fajr wake him up
in fact from the night
help him be able to
sleep early
so that waking up for Fajr
will not be of a burden
go with him
especially for Salatul Fajr
you might be at work
at Zuhr and Asr
but you can call him to ask
daddy
it is time for Zuhr
have you observed Zuhr
or should I call one of my
younger ones
to bring you water
are you going to the masjid
it will be a kind of a
reminder
and pressure upon
goodness for him